easyodds.com 2017-11-19

# Privacy Policy | easyodds.com

easyodds.com Limited is an service and information provider - it is not a betting company. The principle sports betting related web site owned by easyodds.com limited, namely [www.easyodds.com](https://www.easyodds.com/) as well the principle poker related web site, namely [www.pokerverdict.com](https://www.pokerverdict.com/) do not accept any form of wagers. Rather, they provide users with expert information and 'community' services and features.

Notwithstanding the above, easyodds.com Limited is committed to using its best efforts to ensure compliance with "The Internet Gambling Prohibition Act" which was successfully attached to "The Safe Port Act" and passed by the US Senate on Friday 29 September 2006.

At present, the policy of the Company is to take the following precautions:

  1. We do not accept member sign-ups from residents of the USA.
  2. We do not promote or advertise gambling businesses that are resident in the USA.
  3. In instances, where we receive a monetary reward specifically for referring clients to a betting company, in the event that the betting company does accept member sign-ups from residents of the USA, we will not accept any rewards relating to any client that we have inadvertently referred to that betting company who is a resident of the US.

Given the difficulty of stopping general access and the fact that we take active steps to avoid facilitating or profiting from bets made by residents of the USA (as set out in points 1-3 above), residents of the USA are allowed to surf our site as non-members.

Given continuing legal evolution, our policy on legal compliance may be updated from time to time, whether in relation to this law or in relation to any other potentially relevant gambling related legislation.

###  Privacy Statement

**easyodds.com**  Limited is committed to protecting your privacy online.

The information we collect from you is used to provide you with the services you wish to access through our website [for example, the betting odds comparison service and the assisted registration service (whereby we send your information to selected betting partners to enable you to open an account with those betting partners)] (together the "Services") and to provide a personalised service to you when you visit our website. At  **easyodds** , we appreciate that you do not want the personal information you provide to us distributed indiscriminately. Below we explain how we collect information, what we do with it and what controls we have.

###  What data do we collect?

So that we can provide the Services, we may, upon registration or at other times, ask you to submit information such as your name, e-mail address, postal address, telephone number and credit or debit card number and expiration date. You are under no obligation to provide such information. However, if you should choose to withhold requested information, we may not be able to provide you with the Services.

###  How is the information used?

**easyodds**  will use the information you provide to us to:-

  * identify visitors;
  * provide the Services;
  * verify your credit/debit card details;
  * improve the content of our web page;
  * customise the content and/or layout of our page for each individual customer; and
  * send you information we think you may find useful, including information about new products and Services.

We may occasionally send you direct mail about products and Services we feel may be of interest to you. This will only come from us (or our agents) and only if you have indicated that you do not object to these offers. You can, however, tell us not to do so, by sending an e-mail message to [support@easyodds.com](mailto:support@easyodds.com?subject=General%20Enquiry).

###  With whom is the information shared?

If you use the assisted registration service it will be necessary for  **easyodds**  to disclose your personal information to the betting partners whom you indicate that you would like to open an account with. The betting partners will then use that data in accordance with their own privacy policy (links will be provided to such privacy policies when you use the assisted registration service). By using the assisted registration service, you consent to such use of that information and agree that  **easyodds**  are not responsible for such use.

**easyodds**  may disclose aggregate statistics about our site visitors, customers and sales in order to describe our Services to prospective partners, advertisers and other reputable third parties and for other lawful purposes, but these statistics will include no personally identifying information.

**easyodds**  may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or if it believes that such action is necessary to protect and defend the rights, property or personal safety of  **easyodds** , the site or its visitors.

This site contains links to other sites.  **easyodds**  is not responsible for the privacy policies or the content of such sites.

###  Log files / IP addresses

When you visit our Site, we automatically log your IP address (the unique address which identifies your computer on the internet) which is automatically recognised by our web server. We use IP addresses to help us administer the Site and to collect broad demographic information for aggregate use. Your IP address may be linked to any personally identifiable information that you submit.

##  Security

**easyodds**  places a great importance on the security of all personally identifiable information associated with our customers. We have security measures in place to attempt to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of customer data under our control. We use secure server software (SSL) to encrypt financial information you input before it is sent to us. While we cannot ensure or guarantee that loss, misuse or alteration of data will not occur, we use our best efforts to prevent this.

###  Use of cookies

Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to your hard drive to store and sometimes track information about you. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but if you prefer, you can change your browser to prevent that. However, you may not be able to take full advantage of a website if you do so. Cookies are specific to the server that created them and cannot be accessed by other servers, which means they cannot be used to track your movements around the web. Although they do identify a user's computer, cookies do not personally identify users and passwords and credit card information are not stored in cookies.

We may use cookies to:-

  * identify who you are and to access your account information;
  * estimate our audience size and patterns;
  * ensure that you are not asked to register twice;
  * control how often visitors see similar ads;
  * track preferences and to improve and update our website; and
  * track the progress and number of entries in some of our promotions and contests.

###  Where is the information stored

Information which you submit via this web site is initially sent to a computer located in the United Kingdom. However, in the course of processing your personal information in accordance with this privacy policy it may be necessary to transfer your personal information outside the EEA. Please contact us if you wish to know the details of the countries involved.

###  Advertisements on the easyodds Site

**easyodds**  allows third parties to provide banner advertisements within this site. Because your web browser must request those advertising banners from those third parties, they may record your IP address for certain purposes. If you would like to prevent these third parties from doing this, you should visit each third party's site individually and opt-out (if this option is offered by the third parties in question).

###  Your acceptance of these terms

By using this site, you consent to the collection and use of information by  **easyodds**  and to the use of that information in accordance with the  **easyodds**  privacy policy. If we change our privacy policy in any way, we will post these changes on this page.

###  Your rights

You have a legal right to a copy of all the personal information about you held by us. You also have a right to correct any errors in that information. As mentioned above, you have a right to prevent us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes.

Please email any questions, concerns or comments you have about these policies to [info@easyodds.com](mailto:info@easyodds.com?subject=General%20Enquiry). Alternatively call us on 0207 751 4479, or write to us at:

**easyodds.com**  Limited  
115 Design Centre East  
Chelsea Harbour  
London  
SW10 0XF

©  **easyodds.com**  Limited 2016
